https://data-flair.training/blogs/python-interview-questions/

71 Python Interview Questions and Answers [New] – Get Ready for Technical Round
Q8. -- to explain del and remove
Q.10
Q.14. Explain try, raise, and finally.
Q.15. What happens if we do not handle an error in the except block?
Q.18. Explain the problem with the following piece of code-
Q.19. What do you see below?
Q.31. Where will you use while rather than for?